englishpractice.com 2000-12-13

# EnglishPractice - Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for EnglishPractice

EnglishPractice.com Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: EnglishPractice.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

This site contains links to other sites. **EnglishPractice** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use an outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

EnglishPractice works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how 24/7 Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.247media.com/privacy.html>

This site uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages.  To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies.  To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy/privacy.htm>

Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by our Web advertising partner, Sonar Network, using DoubleClick's DART technology. Please click here for more information on Sonar Network and its privacy policy, information collected in the process of delivering an ad to you and your choices regarding delivery of targeted ad campaigns.  <http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm>

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact   
[info@englishpractice.com](mailto:info@englishpractice.com)   EnglishPractice Inc. Suite 300, 500 - 4 Avenue SW Calgary, Alberta T2P 2V6 Canada info@englishpractice.com
